Guide to the North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
- Photographs, 1969-2010; 1969 2010
  - Photographic Prints, 1969-1998; 1969 1998
    - Mankiller, Wilma, undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Marching Band, 1983-1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Marijuana, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Martial Arts, 1989, 1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Martin, Charles, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day, 1989-1994 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Mayor of Raleigh Tom Feltzer, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - McGovern, George, undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - McKimmon Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Meetings, 1995, undated (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Merchant's Mill Pond (includes negatives), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Metcalf Faculty Social, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Midway Airlines, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Mitch's Tavern, 1983, undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Mocktails, undated (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Morgan and Maddog in the Morning, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Motorcycles and Mopeds, 1982, undated (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Moving, 1990, 1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Mt. Rogers (negatives), undated (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Mt. Wash (includes negatives), undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Mud Wrestling, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Mugs (headshots) - contact sheets, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Mugs (headshots) - faculty, staff, 1988-1994, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Mugs (headshots) - miscellaneous, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Mugs (headshots) - negatives, 1994, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Mugs (headshots) - students, 1993, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Mugs (headshots) - unlabeled (1 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Mugs (headshots) - unlabeled (2 of 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Music, 1992-1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Mystery Science 3000, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - NAACP Meeting?, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - National Society of Black Engineers, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Native American Festival, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - New Horizons Choir, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - New York, 1980-1994? (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Newlin, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - News and Observer, 1989, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Nimoy, Leonard, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Nixon, Richard, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - North Carolina Museum of History, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - North Carolina Public Television, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - North Carolina Solar Center, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - North Carolina State Fair, 1980-1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - North Carolina State University 75th Anniversary, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - North Carolina State University 100th Anniversary, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - North Carolina Student Legislature, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Nowicki Exhibit, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Nuclear Engineering, 1989, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Olympics (Torch Relay and Metcalf Mania Olympics), 1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - O'Quin, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Orientation, 1993, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Oscar Meyer Weiner, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Ozturk, Mehmet, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Pagan Religion, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Pan-African Week, 1989, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Parking Decks, 1974-1993 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Pastan, Linda, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - PAWS Walk, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - PE 100, 1996, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Peace Corps, 1990,1994 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Pepsi Promotional Materials (includes slides), 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Perot, Ross, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Photographers, 1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Physical Plant, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Phytotron, undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Pipes and Drums, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Pizza Hut, undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Poetry Readings, 1994, undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Poulton, B.R., undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Poultry Feeder, undated (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - POW and MIA Vigil, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - President's Helicopter and Airplane, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Vistis, 1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Price, Vincent, 1981, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Print Shop, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Protests, 1988-1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations Student Society of America, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Public Safety, 1989, 1991, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Pullen Park, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Pulp Production, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Pyro Man, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Quayle, Dan, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Railroad Tracks, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Raleigh Christmas Parade, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Raleigh Renaissance Festival, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Rambeau, Charles, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Rathskeller, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Ray, Charles Promotional Materials, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Reactor Control Room, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Recycling, 1989, 1994, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Reggae Festival, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Registration, 1982-1993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Republicans, 1982, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Restaurants, 1986-1994, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Right Touch Phones, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Roberts, Oral, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Rodeo Team, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Rollerblading, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Rollins, Yvonne, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Roommates, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Rose, Charlie, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Rosenthal, Karen, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - ROTC, 1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Sabbath, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Sagan, Carl, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Sailing Club, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Sales on Campus, 1987, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Sand Castles, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - SCA Meeting, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Science Stories (Features), undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Sears Dorm Decorating Promotional Materials (includes slides), 1997 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Senate Meetings, 1989, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Senior Council, 1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Shearon Harris Nuclear Power Plant, undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - SI Campus Fest, undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Simpkins, Peter, undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Skelton, Red, undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Smoke Stack, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Snow, 1996, undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Soccer, 1989-1996, undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Solar House, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Space and Aviation, 1991, undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Sports Arenas, undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Spring Break (includes negatives), 1988-1993, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Swimming, 1990, 1995, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Strolling Professor Statue, 1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Student Activists, 1989-1996, undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Student Government, undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Student Senate and Candidate Headshots, undated (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Students - Fun on Campus, 1987-1996, undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Student Media photos- Director of Greek Life, group shot, Theta Nu Xi sorority, 2002?, undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Students - Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1986-1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Students - Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1986-1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Students Relaxing, 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Students Studying, 1989-1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Suicide, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Sun Tan Jam, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl, 1991, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Tailgating, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Take Back the Night, 1990, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Tattooing, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Telethon, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Television Station, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Tennis, 1994-1997, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Tennis Courts, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Terminal Velocity Promotion, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Textiles, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Theatres?, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, Joab L., undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Thompson Theatre, 1993, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Tobacco, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Tobacco Tax Protest, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Tornadoes, 1988, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Towing, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Track and Field, 1981-1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Traffic, 1994-1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Transients, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Transportation, 1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Two Guys Restaurant, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Ultimate All-Night Bash, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Umpstead Coalition Festival, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - United States Postal Service, 1988, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - University Dining, 1989-1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - University of North Carolina Band and Protestors, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - University of North Carolina Board of Governors (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - University Scholars, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - University Towers, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Unlabeled Photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Unlabeled Photographs (2 of 2), 1990-1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Used LP's, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Valentine's Day, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Vandalism, 1985, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Veterinary School, 1979-1989, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Veterinary School Olympics, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Veterinary School Open House, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Video Games, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Vietnam Veteran's Memorial Moving Wall, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Vietnamese Night, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Violinist Itzhak Perlman, undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Visual Arts Center, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Volleyballl, 1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Voting and Voter Registration, 1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Walt Disney World College Program, undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Water Polo, undated (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Weather Stories, 1990-1994, undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Weaver, Jack, undated (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Weir, Bruce, undated (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Weisinger-Brown Building, undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - West Campus Jam, undated (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Westinghouse, undated (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - White House Visit, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Williamson, Tony Jr. Memorial Service, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Wilson Creek (includes negatives), August 1993 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Witherspoon, Augustus, undated (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - WKNC, 1989-1995, undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Wolfe, Tom, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Wolfram, Walt, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Women's Center, 1994, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Women's Issues, 1993-1994, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Woodchop Project, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Wrestling, 1990, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Yarn (reclaimed), undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Yow, Kay, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Zahn, Margaret A., undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Zoo, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball Photographic Prints, 1970s-1997; 1970 1997
    - Games (1 of 3), 1970s (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Games (2 of 3), 1970s (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Games (3 of 3), 1970s (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Games, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Bill Russell, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - David Thompson, 1975, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Games (1 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Games (2 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Games (3 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Games (4 of 4), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1981-1983, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1981-1983, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Games, practices, and press conferences (1 of 4), 1981-1986, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Games, practices, and press conferences (2 of 4), 1981-1986, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Games, practices, and press conferences (3 of 4), 1981-1986, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Games, practices, and press conferences (4 of 4), 1981-1986, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Games, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Games and practices (1 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Games and practices (2 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Games and practices (3 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Games and practices (4 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Soccer and Baseball, 1983, 1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Games, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1985-1987, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1985-1987, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Games and practices (1 of 4), 1986-1987, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Games and practices (2 of 4), 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Games and practices (3 of 4), 1986-1987, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Games and practices (4 of 4), 1986-1987, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Practices, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Games and candlelight vigil, 1987-1988, 1993, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Pete Maravich days before his death, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Headshots and team photos, 1988-1989, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Practices, pre-season exhibitions, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Game notes, statistics, coaches' quotes (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Game notes, statistics, coaches' quotes (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Exhibition games and practices (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition games and practices (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Games and practices (1 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Games and practices (2 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Games and practices (3 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Games and practices, including women's basketball (1 of 2), 1990, 1995-1997, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Games and practices, including women's basketball (2 of 2), 1990, 1995-1997, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Games and practices, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Games (1 of 2), 1992-1993, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Games (2 of 2), 1992-1993, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Men's Basketball vs. North Carolina, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Virginia (1 of 3), 1995? (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Virginia (2 of 3), 1995? (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Virginia (3 of 3), 1995? (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Virginia and North Carolina, 1995? (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Cartoon of Jim Valvano, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Headshots of players and coaches from other ACC teams, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Sports Graphics, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Negatives, Contact sheets, and Slides, 1987-2003; 1987 2003
  This series contains three subseries: Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Slides. The majority of the negatives and contact sheets are arranged alphabetically according to the first name of the photographer. The remaining folders in each subseries are arranged alphabetically by subject. The slides are arranged alphabetically by subject, with the unlabeled and undated slides placed at the end.
  - Negatives, 1991-2003
    - AJW - Athletics (1 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - AJW - Athletics (2 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - AJW - Athletics (3 of 3), 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - AJW - Campus groups and events, Features, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Andrew Knopp, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Andrew Knopp, Carl Hudson, Dave Kuzdroll, and various others [includes slides] (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Andrew Knopp, Carl Hudson, Dave Kuzdroll, and various others [includes slides] (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Angela - Athletics, Romeo and Juliet, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Angela Williams - Allen Keys, Athletics, DC, Rock the Vote, State Fair [includes 1 sheet of slides] (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Aryn - Open House; Marty - Shack-a-thon, Halloween Bash; John - Tennis; Nicole B. - Undergraduate Symposium, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Ashley Britt - Dog Olympics, Open House, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Ashley Britt - Features, various campus shots (1 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Ashley Britt - Features, various campus shots (2 of 2) [includes 1 sheet of slides], 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Ashley Britt - Photostories [with notes], 1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Austin Dowd, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Ben Austin, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Boyle - Athletics, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Bradley Michael - Football, State Fair, campus shots, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Brandy Callahan, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Brent Horton - AKA House, Provost, Solar Generators, Volleyball, and others, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Brent Horton - Athletics, Fair, Move-in, Susan B. Anthony Dinner, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Brooke Heuts - Features, Women's Studies 10th Anniversary, Volleyball, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Brooks Stout - Features, State Fair, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Christina Hammock - African-American Heritage Society, Alumni Association, Athletics, Fair, Features, Stroud Center, World AIDS Day, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Christopher Dappert, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Crystal - Athletics, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Curris - Ladies in Red; Yukchi Cheung - College of Management, 2001, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Dan - Athletics, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Dan Riggsbee- Athletics, Centennial Campus, Glee Club, Habitat for Humanity, MLK Night, Music, PAMS, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Dave - Athletics, Bricks, Engineering, India Festival, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - David Thompson - Athletics, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - DBS - Men's Basketball vs. Australia, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - EEB, First Union, Project #3, 1991, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Elizabeth Wallup - Design School, International Night, March on Capital, Shack-a-thon, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Erica Tuers - Athletics, Asia Night, Concert, Craft Fair, Dracula, Jazz, New Horizon, Study Abroad Fair, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Erik Snyder, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Febin Skaria, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Flora - First Feature Shots; Brickyard ROTC; Bravard, NC, 1996, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Gigi Cheung - Athletics, Bug-O-Rama, Crossroads, DC, Fair, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Gigi Cheung - Athletics, Campus, 27,000 Stories, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Gigi Cheung - Athletics, Crossroads, Natural Resource College, Snow Day, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Gigi Cheung - Men's Basketball, Brickyard [professionally developed photos], undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Gigi Cheung - Men's Basketball, Brickyard [professionally developed negatives], undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Grayson C., 2002 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Hardy, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Hart - Athletics, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Harvey - Athletics, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Heather Ball - Campus, Wolfline, State Fair, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Iyare - Athletics, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Iyare - Athletics, Hurricane Floyd, Jimmy V Golf (Michael Jordan), other campus shots, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Iyare - Athletics; Hurricane Floyd; King, NC; other campus shots, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Iyare - Bell Tower, Faculty Senate, Indian Pow-wow, NROTC, Pan-Africa, Playboy, Tunnel, other campus shots (1 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Iyare - Bell Tower, Faculty Senate, Indian Pow-wow, NROTC, Pan-Africa, Playboy, Tunnel, other campus shots (2 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Iyare - Graduation, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - J. Malecky - Athletics, Senior Profiles, 1998, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - J. Searle - Athletics, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Jake - Athletics, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Jake - Features, various campus events, 1997, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Jamie - Athletics, Features, Graduation, Holladay Building, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Jamie - Athletics, Fair, Graduation, Jimmy V Golf, other campus shots, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Jamie - Snow, Swimming, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - James Curle (1 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - James Curle (2 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - James Curle (3 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - James Curle (4 of 4), 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - James Farlow [includes slides], 2003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Jana - Athletics, Blood Drive, Dog Olympics, CALS/911, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Jana - Athletics, Buildings, Fair, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Jana - Baseball, Hillsborough Street, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Jason Bostic - Beulaville, NC; Campus Shots; Construction; Hurricane Floyd; Jimmy V Golf (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Jay Brown, Jake, DC, Feature, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Jeff Mc C. - Campus/Lorax, untitled, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Jeffrey McAfee - Campus Shots, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Jeffrey McAfee - Athletics, Employee Appreciation, Technology Expo, Windhover, other campus shots, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Jen James - Lawn Party, Rip Van Winkle, Sandblast, Vet School, Wind Ensemble, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Jen James - Athletics, Madrigal Dinner, State Fair, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Jen M. - Athletics, State Fair, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Jennie Smith - Features, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Jennifer Reed - Cross Country, Minor Music Recital, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Jennifer S./J. Swartz - Athletics, Features, 1996-1997, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Jim C. - Athletics, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Joe Hall - Athletics, BeBop Concert, Reggae Fest, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Joey Luther - Athletics (1 of 2), 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Joey Luther - Athletics (2 of 2) [includes slides], 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Joey Luther - Athletics, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Joey Luther - Band, Brickyard Organization Fair, Carroll Hall, Cat Kidneys, Mural, Student Senate, Valentines Day, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Joey Luther - Baseball, Beach Blast, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - John Borwick? - Budget Cut March, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - John Moran - Dog Olympics, Hurricane, other campus events, 1999-2001 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - John Stogner - Athletics, 1998-1999, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)